Thank you for watching!
Hello!
We started with the mysterious Pen Myinta...
I'll greet you right away.
It's morning time, and we are...
We are CJ Mischudo.
We're CJ Mischudo.
Did you see that?
Sister.
Younger sister
The online signing session has started!
Stroking, stroking, stroking!
It's a great stroke!
Hello, hello, hello!
By the way, what was Yu's pose just now?
Upa-lupa-lupa!
Isn't it cute?
I was doing it like this.
I see.
Hello.
Thank you very much for Miyuki.
Thank you very much.
Small mouth!
Yes, thank you very much.
Hey, now, yesterday...
You pretended yesterday, right, after you cut it off,
You've never met him before, right?
Mr. Bob Laima.
Yes.
Bob Laima.
Bob Laima?
I'm so happy to wash my hair in such a short time.
It dries quickly, too.
It's very fast.
I love it.
I like taking a bath.
Taking a bath.
But if it takes 10 or 15 minutes, I'm done.
If it takes 15 minutes.
That's really fast.
It's nice. I'm jealous of your long mints, though.
As I mentioned earlier, there was a free concert yesterday.
Yes.
How was it?
Yes, it was good.
I think the best one was in the next round.
Yes, it was. Up until now, you used to play only two new songs at a time.
Now you have 3 songs at once.
And the Jidosha Dorren is different, too.
The song "Eminer" had never been performed by 10 members before, and it was the first time for the five of us to perform it together.
It was a difficult and challenging song, how did you all like it?
How was it? Improvement.
It was fun, wasn't it?
What? Where did you improve?
It was fun. The day before the outing, I went back to him, and we drove there,
I was sleeping a lot when I decided to go and take a look around,
Sleeping?
So cute.
I was lucky to be there when I realized.
But it's nice.
When you are a guide model.
Yes, it is. My friends came, my brother, my grandma, and a girl who was a junior at school.
I met my brother and grandma.
I met them for the first time.
She was very interesting.
Yes, she was.
She told me that Yamae-chan is cute.
Yuno's brother is a fan of Mirei.
Really? That's amazing.
I see.
He's not a fan of Yuno.
Grandma turned me over.
Her stomach.
So, a junior high school student came to see me, and she was in the first grade when Yuno was in the third grade,
She said she had been cheering for me all the time.
Oh, I'm so glad to hear that.
They went to the same school.
Satsuka was happy because they are from different schools. She said that everyone had a good expression on their faces.Satsuka was happy because it was different. She said everyone looked good.
That's right. The song under this shoot was different.
You know, we did it.
I did quite a bit.
But this time, the song has a pretty cute look,
I thought I would be able to capture their cute faces,
It was too bright.
It was pretty sunny.
Are you okay, us?
The weather was fine.
It's so bright.
Didn't you look like that? Everyone.
It was nice weather, wasn't it?
Yes, it was.
It felt good.
It was bright.
Hey.
I was happy.
Because it was raining before that.
Hey.
It was raining. It was raining.
I feel like I'm doing a lot of training.
I do it even on sunny days.
That's for sure.
I am challenging myself in many ways.
I feel like I'm growing.
How was it for you, Yuna?
It was my first time. You landed in Aichi Prefecture, right?
Yes, it was.
We are flying in the air over Aichi Prefecture.
It was the first time for you to land on the ground.
How was it? What was Aichi like on the ground?
When I came to Tokyo, I had never been to an Aeon before.
So when I went to the AEON in Aichi, I really felt like I was in Fukuoka.
You felt Fukuoka?
Aichi is different?
But the AEON mall in Tsunedame is amazing.
Tokyo is small, right? All of Tokyo is small.
I was surprised at how big it was.
The AEON Mall in Tsunedame was huge.
They put a lot of snacks and candies at the school, which made me really happy.
From konjac jelly to all kinds of things.
I ate nothing from konjac jelly.
From konjac jelly to what?
We were given everything from konjac jelly to juice.
After the concert, we had a little sweets party with everyone.
Thank you very much.
I think we got to know each other pretty well.
That's for sure.
Even after the show.
What do you think?
Different outfits?
The three of us?
I think we are getting to know each other much better than when we first met.
I'm glad. I'm glad.
And Yuna?
We were so busy with lessons that we didn't have time to have dinner together,
But during the free live period, we had more meals together,
I feel like we eat a lot.
We don't have that much time at all.
We also go out after lessons a lot.
I think that's how close we have become.
That's for sure.
That's good.
I would like to ask you what your impression was when you first joined us and what it is like now.
The three of us.
To be frank, not at all.
Shall we start with Cocona?
Cocona.
I was a little scared at first.
I understand.
I was a little scared,
But now I think she's cute when she spoils me sometimes.
I see.
And then there's the older sister thing.
She's kind to me, like she puts things together for me.
She brings things together.
She is the oldest of them all.I'm the oldest of them all.
I'm doing it.
Cocona is scary, to be honest.
The family is being honest.
I understand.
Don't understand.
I'll tell you that.
I was scared too.
I don't know how to say it.
She seemed pretty girly.
That's for sure.
My first conversation with her was very gal,
I don't know how to say it.
The way she talked was like a huge yokai.
A yokai.
And she's a big sister and mature, so I was really nervous.
And now?
I don't get nervous now.
I think it's interesting.
The words that people say are very interesting.
Do you understand?
I do.
Do you?
What about Yuno?
I don't think Yuno has changed much since we first met.
She hasn't changed at all.
She seems calm.
You got along with each other quickly at first, didn't you?
Yes, we did. Very much so.
Like the way you were always making a move on him.
That's surprisingly attractive, isn't it?
Yes, he is. She's very attractive.
Yuna Sparkling JK.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Kira Kira JK.
What about Yuna?
Well, who puts their knees up?
Don't do that.
I'm with you.
You do the reverse knee kakko sometimes, right? From the front.
It doesn't go down.
I don't know what you're talking about.
It's hard for me to react.
And it's funny that they do it not to us, but to their older sisters.
I don't think anyone else does it.
That's for sure.
So, who gets down on their knees?
Impression?
That hasn't changed.
It's the same.
At first, I thought she would be more fluffy,
But then I thought she was more like an older lady.
She was a big sister.
She was, wasn't she?
That's right.
Let's ask her about her impression of Nonaka.
Nonaka was the same age as me, after all,
We were the same age,
I had the strongest impression that she was my senior.
Wait a minute.
This is bad.
I'm not that strong.
He's too mature,
Yuna and I have been talking about it,
I don't feel like we're the same age.
From our point of view,
Too mature,
He was our senior.
If we didn't talk, we wouldn't be in junior high.
But..,
I mean, it was exciting,
The excited part is very junior high school-like.
He was the most excited of the five of us.
Because of their high voices.
Even from Yuna and the others' point of view,
Nonaka and Emi don't look the same age.You don't look the same age as Nonaka and Emaibu, do you?
No, they don't.
How do you like it?
The first time I met him, he was very mature and had high hands, so I was very nervous to stand next to him.
Isn't the pressure amazing?
Wait!
He seemed like a senior.
I see.
Do you feel like you have to teach them?
I don't know if I have to teach them, but it's only been about a year and a half since I joined the company,
I don't want to teach you anything weird, so I'm sure you'll learn from your older sister members,
So I thought I would not tell you this strange thing.
Weird thing?
Is this the one who is asking?
I want to hear the opposite.
Emma Yudayan.
That's for sure.
Emma is,
I've been guessing since the audition, right?
Yeah...
I kept my eyes open.
Her eyes were open.
That's scary.
Scary.
I love it.
I'm scared.
I thought he was amazing, and I thought he was magnificent. From the audition.
It's so hooded.
I'm not hooded.
I'm into it.
But when I talked to him, he was very calm and composed,
I felt like he was a new member.
Really.
But when we talked, he seemed flustered, but he was the kind of person you wanted to hug.
He is an amazing presence.
She's amazing.
You know what I mean? It's like the best material.
Oh, no...
I'll stay away from you.
You know what I mean? It makes you want to hug it.
It's a facial reflection.
That's amazing.
Really?
I like it.
Thank you.
And Yunan is so cute.
And I wondered what she was like.
There was a high pitch when I was auditioning.
I had, but she's pretty independent, isn't she?
Yes!
I thought so.
You didn't even tell your sister members what to do,
I thought that I wanted you to say that,
I wanted him to say that.
I did.
I think it's really cool,
And YoonA is so confident.
That's for sure.
There's something about you,
I've seen you on the radio with him,
I really think it's the first time.
I've seen you so many times, so I'm really impressed with your calmness.
Yay!
He must be smart.
That's the image I have of him.
What do you think? From Yuto's point of view.
Now, when I saw you at the audition, I thought for sure that you were a very sparkling type of person.
You know what I thought? I really thought so.
I felt the same smell.
Yes, I did. I thought she was the same type of person, a different type of sparkling person.
I thought he wasn't too sparkly.
What?
In a good way.
He was very easy to talk to.
So, the hard-to-talk-about type of sparkle?
The type of sparkle that makes it hard to talk about at first.
That's great.That's great.
Because when we met to audition for this place, only one of us had a curtain.
That's right.
It's amazing.
It's like an amazing dome.
No, it's not. I told you I was just trying to be cool at first.
My impression of you is good.
What's your impression of Yuna?
Yuna's scared of pretty girls.
You know what I mean?
I get it.
I wondered what kind of character she was because of her cuteness.
It was strange, wasn't it?
I mean, it's not like she's chatting with a stuffed animal,
It's like I'm holding a stuffed animal.
I see.
That's the image I have of all cute girls.
In Yuna's mind.
And then, unexpectedly, I feel like I'm going to slash them with a stuffed animal sword.
It's scary.
You're surprisingly rough.
Rough.
It's very rough.
That's for sure.
He was easy to talk to, in a good way.
Both of them.
I'm an energetic person.
I'm an actress, but I'm too calm.
She's calmer than I am.
I don't know if it's because I'm calmer.
You're the calmest?
I'm always upset.
You're upset.
Sometimes I hide it, sometimes I don't hide it at all, but I'm upset all the time.
You want to tell me? Emma.
Emma is really something.
She's always been so firm and calm.
Like she's surprised or something.
I've never seen her get so upset.
I think that's great.
Also, she seems like she's easy to talk to.
I feel like I'm going to get along with everyone soon.
It's definitely a universal feeling.
Yeah, it's a good vibe.
It's nice.
That's nice.
I see.
YoonA is really smart.
She knows so much.
Emma said...
You know, when Emma was staying at the paper house with us.
She said it was too hard for her to speak.
She said she couldn't do what she couldn't say.
Lately I'm starting to understand.
Everything she does...
You act so smart.
Oh, yeah, I do.
Sometimes you act crazy.
That's why
I thought it was great.
That's great.
Actually, MN, do you ever get impatient?
Sure, I do.
Yes, I do.
Do you look at what you see?
I see Genna a lot.
I'm like, "Genna, what am I going to do?
Yes, it is. Like the sister members,
I'm like, "What am I going to do?
Oh, I forgot.
They say I'm cute.
I'm sure.
You say I'm cute.
I'm saying she's cute.
What about Emma?
She doesn't show it, but inside she's very nervous and nervous about what to do.
She is.
Maya told me before that I'm the type of person who doesn't show.
She said it so casually.
When I get nervous, I think the corners of my mouth get really tight.
That's true.Indeed.
There is a force in it. If you look closely, the place looks like it has a lot of power.
It seems to be the type that doesn't come out.
The type that won't come out. It's a bit like Riko's. A little.
Don't you feel it?
It's been almost two years now, and I still don't get it. I don't know.
I think I know what you are at first.
I don't know.
But even now, there are still many things I don't understand.
Not yet. About half.
You haven't even said half.
About a quarter.
There are still a lot of things that the older members don't know yet.
That's true.
I see.
We talked about our impressions of each other.
We became good friends.
You are changing more and more again, aren't you?
That's right.
On the contrary, you know, since the audition here,
Coconner has changed a lot, hasn't he?
It's like you've done a callao.
Is that true? I don't know. Your impression of yourself?
Impressions, you know, in humor. The three of you?
Two. Yeah.
You just asked me that.
That's all I told you before. We did.
Okay, I'll keep it short.
But after MV came in, both of them were saying that I should be a big sister to them.
As seniors, it's just a little difference,
It's just a little difference,
But they are saying what they were told by their older sister members that I have to tell them,
I'm really grateful for that.
I feel like I have a little bit of leeway now. Me too.
You were nervous about everything.
I'm out.
Everything.
But I was nervous because there were five of us, so I felt safe.
You know, the three of us got to know each other better after MN joined the group.
We met in the middle of the group, but we didn't get along well.
But this one was too strong.
In a different direction.
Because of their strong personalities.
Even though we clash.
Our lives are too different.
It's been a tough year. Really.
Really.
It was really tough.
It was surprising.
Two new members came in and we were in harmony.
Thank you so much.
Chili girl was in.
Thank you very much.
We still have a free concert.
May 1 is the last one.
Osaka Nanko ATC.
Please come and join us.
It's a free live concert.
There will also be a benefit hall.
There will also be a Kyushu Metropolis and a farewell party, so please come.
Please come.
And it's graduation season, isn't it?
That's right.
Gumi graduated from junior high school.
Shimogumi?
Shimo-gumi.
I'm going to be Gumi from now on.
Gumi from now on?
That's right.
I see.
How about you, Gumi?
No one found out I was fingering myself until the end of the graduation ceremony.
Really?
You graduated. What about your goal of not wanting to be found out?
They did. But gradually, my desire to have it exposed grew stronger and stronger.
What?
I wanted to be exposed as soon as possible,
In the end, no one approached me at the graduation ceremony,
What?What?
What about the pictures?
Like, "You're so cute"?
There weren't any.
What?
Congratulations.
That was it.
She's a little bit of a shy person at school,
We really get along...
No, no.
I just took the fact that we were close and no one ever found out.
It's not like they're keeping it quiet or anything,
They're aware of it.
I'm sure there are fans who saw you wearing glasses before,
Oh, I see. Oh, so you wear glasses at school.
You really are a different person.
That's why they didn't notice.
Do they still send you colored papers?
I didn't get any colored papers.
I received them for one day at the beginning of March, and that was the last time.
It was really interesting.
It said, "We can graduate together, right?
What about Ema?
What? I graduated as usual.
I cried.
Ema is going to cry.
She seems to be very neutral, doesn't she? School life.
We all cried together with the song,
After that, we took pictures of various things and finished.
The graduation ceremony was the complete opposite of what I expected.
But I really admire Yuna's kind of gap between school and activities like this.
That's for sure.
She's a super shy person at school, but when she goes out, she's super cute,
I really admire Yuna who is super shy in school but super cute when she goes out.
That's for sure. That's the moment my friends noticed,
You write a lot.
What? Really? Like that.
I adore it.
Are you graduating soon, Nonaka?
That's right.
I'm really getting a lot of advice from the teachers.
Various things.
There you go, serious.
Yes, that's right. No, no, no. It's not that I'm too serious,
It's not that I'm serious, it's just that my teacher and my friends are too aggressive.
That's great.
I saw this delivery, and they said, "This is what I saw, so you should do it better.
They were watching me,
So I don't know. I think I'm more like Ema.
I think I'm more like Ema,
I wonder.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yes, I am. Looking forward to it.
Do you feel lonely?
I do feel sad, but I would like to start junior high school all over again.
Not at all.
What about Coconner? Like in junior high school?
Junior high school?
At graduation.
I cried in the mud.
Really?
I was beaten.
I knew it.
I'm the type of person who lives for that.
I really cried,
I was sobbing as I sang.
It was a really good memory.
We were at the school building, taking pictures while everyone was mingling,
We took a lot of pictures of things we don't talk about, like it was the last time.
And also, I was working with another group at that time, so I was able to have an autograph session.
I asked him for his autograph and we had an autograph session.
Oh, wow!
We had an autograph session.
Wow, that's great.
Sounds like fun.
Yes, it is. That made me happy.
Eh~?
What about Yu?Yu no?
No one cried at Yu no.
Well, we're part of the middle and high school system, so we'll all be in the same high school class after graduation anyway,
Oh, I see.
So it was just a graduation ceremony to mark the end of the school year,
Yuno didn't cry either,
We just took pictures and went home.
I didn't feel sad.
There was no loneliness.
Oh, I see.
But if we had been together...
Well, you know, there was a comment that bothered me earlier.
I was wondering if you can advance to the next grade.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Eh~.
But it's a little fluffy, isn't it?
That's true.
I can do it, too.
Yu no wa, I got all the signatures just in time,
Just in time?
Just barely.
That's dangerous.
Coconan was also last minute, you know, when he was getting paid, right?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
We did it together, together.
Right.
That's right.
But you know, I'm glad. We can get a new grade. We don't have to worry about staying in school.
We're all going to high school.
Oh, high school.
JK.
Everyone is JK.
I guess that means there will be no more active junior high school students.
So it's too soon again. They're gone.
That was quick.
JK.
She disappeared right away.
She disappeared.
But you know, since we are all going to be high school students, I want to do something. Something typical of high school.
Surely.
I want to go to Disney in my school uniform.
I want to go to Disney.
I want to go while I'm still in high school.
It's been a year.
I haven't done it.
I graduated high school, so next time.
So. It's a surrender.
That's right. So, during this year, I'm going to get a uniform.
I want to go with you guys.
I thought right away that I wanted to go.
I thought that right away. Something to do in private.
I'd like to go with a project or something.
When I said I wanted to go as part of a project, I was in the middle of a huge struggle.
I was in the middle of a long lost project, and I was able to escape from the neck.
I want to do it.
What do you want to do? When I'm in high school.
I want my friends to find out when I'm in high school.
I don't want to be found out.
I want to graduate, graduate, and then I want to be a fulfilled, you know, sparkling JK.
Kira Kira JK.
Do people who use the term "Kira Kira JK" want to become Kira Kira JK?
I want to be.
I was at the entrance ceremony because it was the day of the concert.
That's why I was already like that when I missed the entrance ceremony.
I didn't get off to a good start.
Entrance ceremony is important.
Entrance ceremony.
Let's attend it.
Do your best for the entrance ceremony.
I thought it would be bad if it conflicts with the spring tour.
It's an important rehearsal.
You should show that you want to have friends there.
Make lots of friends.
I want you to ask me one question.
What is it?
I made friends during the exam.
What?
I don't understand.
That was fast.That was fast.
We didn't even know if we would be accepted yet, but we came to take the test.
I was waiting for the interview.
The girl next to me looked really nervous, so I asked her if she was nervous.
Intense.
She was so superior.
Even though I was going to take the interview later.
I'm nervous.
What? What are you saying? I'm imagining it.
So we went home together and became friends.
That's great.
We talked about it.
I'm glad.
I want to make, I want to make friends.
On the other hand, are there people who say, "I graduated from junior high school" or "I graduated from high school"?
Certainly.
There are a lot of people who have graduated from college or high school.
Is it spring break?
It's that time of the year. Isn't it early?
It's really early.
It's already the third year of high school. It's the second year of high school.
Second year of high school?
Aren't you in elementary school?
A whole year is a period of time.
But it's hard to imagine graduating from elementary school.
That's true.
That's fast.
And the older sister members, too, more and more.
Congratulations to those who have graduated from college or high school.
Congratulations.
I heard that their children are graduating.
That makes me happy.
Nowadays, there is a lot of talk in the news about individuals taking off their masks.
The field is also a graduation ceremony.
Yes, I was told that since the school doesn't allow culture, but I was asked to take it off,
I talked to my mom and dad and they said I wouldn't take it off at least for the last time,
I wear a mask when I sing, but I think I will take it off for the graduation ceremony.
I'm thinking of taking it off for the graduates' class.
After receiving the diploma, you go to the place where the teachers are present and give examples.
That is the most embarrassing part.
Because the teachers are looking at you. It's the first time, right?
NonakaEveryone knows you.
I see.
That's right.
I will be seen by the teacher. After you get it, you're looking at it and you're looking forward to it, right? Right in front of me.
I was embarrassed at that time.
I'm sure.
I still have a mask like this, you know, in junior high school,
We graduated without seeing each other's faces.
But, just for the graduation ceremony, you know, just like Nonaka,
I only wore the mask during the song,
For the first time, they took off their glasses and masks,
Oh! Wow.
Do it,
They're gonna see that you're a super pretty girl.
You'll be exposed.
You only wear a mask when you sing,
I went to the graduation ceremony without having practiced a single time before the ceremony,
I was so grateful that I didn't have to sing because I was wearing a mask.
I sang along just fine,
I sang along to the song just fine, and I made a huge mistake, and only one person said, "Ah!
Yay.
Well, Nonaka-chan.
And graduation.
As I recall, it would be nice if they took off their masks from the entrance ceremony.
But then, on the other hand, I wonder if it's normal to take off the mask after high school.
I don't know...
There are people who will take off their masks in the future, but...
Yes, but once you put it on, don't you want to take it off?
That's true.
So, let's talk about the graduation ceremony.
I'm sorry.
Mask.
Shall we take a picture of you signing in?
Shall we?
This is how the emergency talk went.
Okay, first of all...
The pastel outfit.
I'll start with the pink costume from the new group's live.
I'd like to write my signature.I'd like to sign off on it.
Wow something funny ended up in a weird place.
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
There's so much in here!
I started wearing contacts in middle school.
Oh, my.
I want to pull out a lot of contacts.
Shampoo.
I'll go pull.
I'll go first.
They're saying it's too fast.
Please pull!
Here we go.
Ta-da!
Yes, sir.
Names and comments
Congratulations, Gakki! I am looking forward to participating in Ibaraki Park again this year.
If I have time.
Let's see...
Let's see, let's see...
Wait, Kanji?
I'm looking forward to being able to participate in Ibaraki Park again this year.
If I have time.
In Nakaminato.
Naka Port! So this is what Nakaminato is like.
I'm thinking about eating iwagaki (rock oysters) in Ibaraki.
Please let me know if you have any recommendations.
1. by Sakurai Gundan
Thank you for joining Sakurai Gundan.
What?
Iwagaki, I'm going to Nakaminato.
They are really tasty and fresh, and there are a lot of different kinds of seafood.
Please try the iwagaki for sure.
I don't know what it's called, that rock oyster.
I sent him a message saying I'd like to go here next time.
There are huge raw oysters!
Chukang?
That's where they have that restaurant, somehow. Looks delicious.
Oh, it's Isomarusui-san.
Thank you very much.
I'll pick up the ones at home, too.
Congratulations, Suu-san, you drew this, you have great luck.
Thank you very much.
I'm looking forward to the spring tour.
I'll draw.
Okay.
Min-min-ze-misato!
Thank you very much.
It's gone.
I lost a sentence.
You look so cute today, Emma.
It said "petting", didn't it?
Oh...
What?
Well, well, well, well...
I think I got an NG.
Stroke, stroke, stroke.
Stroked, stroked, stroked.
Let's go to the next one.
Skye, no comment.
I'm still okay there.
Yuna is cute.
I mean, it's a petting stroke.
I'll go for Cocona next.
Thank you, Suzukastella!
It was great to see your singing voice and performance live at the university arts and crafts festival yesterday!
I am looking forward to seeing the Mass training live with my own eyes!
Thank you very much from the beginning of the concert!
I wonder if it's that one... you know, the one from the big concert?
Fuji TV 2
Oh, I see.
Okay, I'll draw Yuu's card too.
I drew two cards.
I can't do it!
Go for it!
Yes, Yuka-chan. I'm cheering for you from Hokkaido. I am looking forward to the tour. Thank you very much.
I'm looking forward to it.I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it. Can we eat something from Hokkaido?
I want some!
Okay, I'll go next time. Koyu-chan.
Thank you Nonaka-chan for always giving me healing and Non-chan for always giving me healing. Since Non-chan became a member, I have been supporting you.
Even when I'm having a hard time, listening to the songs of EBITCHU makes me feel better right away, and EBITCHU is an irreplaceable presence for me.
I started working right after graduating from high school and didn't have much to look forward to,
But thanks to EBITCHU, I always live happily. I will keep doing it from now on. Keep up the good work.
Thank you very much.
I will draw.
I'll draw Sakurai.
Bambi-chan, I am amazed by Emma's magnificent performance, let's go to the world together.
What country do you want to go to? Korea.
Athletes, no problem. USA.
Thank you, Taya-chan, for always supporting us and for your beautiful smile.
Thank you, Younapi. There you are, Mr. Helosi, we are always so impressed with your performance.
Chanchoko is the best! Thank you!
Chanchoko's the best!
Thank you, Megumu-chan!
We're looking forward to seeing you on the spring tour with the new resident lineup.
Thank you very much.
Let's pull it down, let's pull it down, let's pull it down
Let's pull!
Hii-chan, I'll do the Hanamoto. Thank you, I love you. Please do the Hanamoto.
Hii-chan, I'll draw the cherry blossoms.
Mr. Sakurai, you wrote it.
I love it!
Mikuchan, thank you for choosing Ebi Junior High School and joining us as a new member!
Thanks to you, Emma, I can enjoy supporting Ebi Junior High!
I know there's a lot of pressure to carry on Hina-chan's color as Honey-Orange and to be asked to sing a lot of songs.
I'm looking forward to getting to know you better at the live performances.
Thank you very much. I'm glad. I'll do my best.
Nakamura Nakamura, I forgot to put it out earlier. Sorry.
Thank you, Nazo-chan What was your favorite song at the school arts and crafts festival?
Well, the unconfirmed junior high quiz, Super Hero, and my favorite, Maze Chan Chan
Oh, it was so much fun. We had a lot of energy.
Thank you, Yuya. I went to the big concert. I went to the big performance conference. Thank you very much.
I will go to the high tour too. Oh, I am so happy. I'm going to shout a lot because they are going to show their voice too.
By the way, do you think you will be able to find a new house without staying in school? Yes!
I told you!
We talked!
I'm so happy to hear your voice.
I'm so happy.
I want to hear it!
Okay, Yuya, I'll play it for you.
Please play!
Thank you, Minami.
Thank you very much.
I've started to have an Ebichu for Okkake tentatively for the last 7 days.
I haven't been able to go to the field yet, but I will work hard every day so that I can meet you someday.
Thank you very much. I'm so happy.
I'm so happy.
Okay, I'll play next.
I'd like to play for all kinds of people.
Erina-san, I love the sparkling idol Nakamaru very much.
Please continue to shine a lot. I'll be rooting for you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Kira Kira.
Yes, I will play Sakura.
Thank you very much, Moto-kun. Emma's singing ability is amazing, and she did it in "Unidentified Junior High School Student in College Arts x" and "Superhero.
Thank you very much.
I'll pull Nakamura.
Hmm? Cab time?
Yeah.
What do you mean this time?
I'm sorry if I'm wrong.
Mr. Shoutarou?
Shoutarou-san.
Who's there?
Um, that...
I'm Shotaro. Which way do you see me?
The one that looks like it has a ball.
It looks like he's got a catch.
How do you know he's got a ball?
Like this.
Three for the kid.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Isn't that Shoutarou?Shoutarou-san, isn't it?
Shoutarou.
Shoutarou-san, isn't it?
Thank you for everything.
I'm rooting for you.
Thank you very much.
I'll do my best.
Shoutarou-san.
Yes, please.
Thank you very much, Mr. Kentaro.
I am looking forward to many venues I am going to for the first time. I'll do my best to secure tickets!
Oh, I hope. I hope you win for sure. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Sayaka who likes Ko Ara. Hello Inopi. I'm wondering about poses when I take twishots at the unemployed training free live, and I'd like to know if there are any poses you recommend.
Yes, I do. Pose, everyone.
Yes, I am.
Ken-tama wrote. Thank you very much.
I'll go next.
Here we go.
Yes, I will.
Yuka-chan, I'm cheering for you from Hokkaido.
I'm cheering for you from Hokkaido. I am looking forward to the tour.
I'm looking forward to eating Hokkaido's food, too.
Yukkachan. I'm going to the cherry blossoms.
Did you say you're going to the cherry blossoms? Yes, I am.
I'm going.
Imo-san. Thank you very much.
I've decided to go for it. She is still very attractive, but I can't help but look forward to her growth in the future.
His smile makes me happy when I see him, his manly singing voice, and the way he sings and enjoys himself even when he is not singing his own part.
I feel like I'm going to be swamped more and more. I will support them with all my strength.
Let's go, SSA!
Let's go!
What was that? I like that coconut.
What's that?
SSA.
Ha-ha-ha.
That's funny.
Amazing strawberries.
Thank you very much. I will go to Nakamura.
Kiichi, nice to meet you. I became a fan when I saw Yuna at an audition for Ebichu.
I used to live in Fukuoka and I love this place very much.
I look forward to seeing you become an even better idol in the future. I will support you. Thank you very much.
Kiichi-san.
Thank you very much.
Thank you, Babarin. Let's have fun! Thank you very much.
Let's go.
Yay!
Yay.
Oh, Ikeno.
Ikeno.
Atsushi-san, ah, ah, Atsushi-san, I'm rooting for you. Do your best. Thank you.
Oh no, it's my turn now.
Thank you.
Okay, I'm going to pull off the weather.
Here we go.
Here you go.
How do you read that?
Not this one? It's English.
Which one?
It's in English.
Give it to me.
Pea.
It says "Endo." Maybe it's Endo.
Mr. Endo.
I'm sorry if I'm wrong.
Did you discover anything new when you played the No-Photos game?
Well, I found a lot of new things, but...
I don't know.
I didn't realize how much fun it was to meet all the family members
I didn't realize how much fun it was to meet the families in person.
I've been online for a long time.
Thank you for everything.
Keep up the good work.
Mr. Fujita, the impact of the unveiling of the big show was amazing. Is there a song you often hum?
What is it, a humming song?
A humming song, that's what I remember now.
What is it, Anytime Anywhere Anywhere Are You?
I like it a lot. I might hum it.I like it a lot. I might even hum it.
I'm sure there are some that are like that.
That's for sure.
Thank you very much.
Nakamura.
Hello, Okada-san.
What was the most difficult thing about joining Ebichu?
If not, please tell us what you had for lunch today.
It's very hard.
If not, it's very hard.
What was the most difficult thing?
What was the hardest thing?
I was the worst at learning the formations.
That was the hardest part,
As an added bonus, I'll tell you what I had for lunch today.
Yakitori bento.
Yay!
Looks delicious.
It looks good.
The manager bought all kinds of things for me.
I'll have the meat and potatoes.
Yes, thank you, Suyu.
I'm looking forward to seeing you on the spring tour.
I hope you come to Kansai a lot.
I'm going to Osaka for a free live concert, so please come.
Please come.
Thank you very much.
Yes, I'm looking forward to seeing you at the spring tour.
Sumomochan 3.
I regularly watch the video of the 5 year old girl who can cleanly eat Odo's chicken wings.
That video is so addictive.
Maruwarawara.
Thank you, Sumomo. Maruwarawara.
I can certainly understand.
I want to call a lot of people who told me I could get dirty at yesterday's face-to-face meeting a.k.a. degree meeting.
Hey, you're right. I'm jealous of your yakitori bento.
Thank you, Nonokamaru 10 days.
I like Nonokamaru because he looks around a lot at the live performance and there are many moments when I think he might have looked at me.
I like her smiling face. Thank you very much.
This is not Nico. It's Emma.
I'm going.
I'll be right back.
... Oh.
Thank you, UEP.
I've been pushing for it since I was a research student at Stapler.
Thank you very much.
I was so happy when I was able to push for Yama-chan for the first time and attend her live performance at the group leader's festival.
I thought she was the most talented one among the students of STAPLA.
Thank you for joining Ebituyu!
I'll be there to pick up my passport for the free live performance of the second day of the festival, so please wait for me!
Oh! Thank you for coming!
Thank you very much!
I really like your singing voice, Yamachan!
Please keep smiling and smiling and smiling and smiling and smiling and smiling and smiling and smiling and smiling and smiling and smiling and smiling and smiling.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for pushing me for so long
Nakamura, I'll pull for you.
I'm going to 4 places on the spring tour, I'm looking forward to the spring tour!
Four stops, that's great, so many people will be there
This is the guy!
Thank you, Mikurin! I attended Musha Shugyo's free live in Fukuoka!
Thank you so much! I was so happy to see so many people responded to my presentation!
I was so happy to see your reaction when I brought the meeting to the show.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to end the press conference now.
I took two tickets.
Thank you very much.
Oh! It's long.
Oh! A lot. Thank you very much.
Hello everyone of EBICHU.
I became interested in EBICHU after watching the audition for Kokoinonaka and recently became a member of the family.
When I saw the members live for the first time at the Furila in Omiya, I couldn't stop crying when I saw Emayuna's effort in Kokoinonaka.
I was so happy when I got a passport with the Yunapi pose.
I am really looking forward to the first day of the spring tour, which will be the first post for the live of Ebichu.
Let's definitely go to Ikimichi with all the Jinin Ebichu and family members.
Let's do our best.
I'll go next time.
Oh! I've been here longer, too. Thank you very much.OH!!! I am long too. Thank you very much.
Mr. Qutaro.
After participating in the Akita Bunko University Arts and Crafts Festival under Prabeth Omiya Furai, my whole family...
Black...what's this?
Hmm?
Black...black tiger!
Black tiger, I became a member. That's right.
My 3 year old daughter is steadily learning to sing Voyager.
I'm looking forward to the future and the activities of the Ebituaries and the Ebituaries,
I am energized every day by following what the 10 of us are doing every day.
I am really looking forward to the spring tour, and I will do my best to support them until I can participate in SSA.
Thank you very much. Please come to the spring tour.
Yes, I'm on my way. Ladies and gentlemen
How do you read this?
bewitching
Mayama-san is too bewitching. Nico is a cute picture match.
I love Yuna-chan with her too cute beauty and voice, Maya picture is Yuna-oshi.
I will post from Morioka and my hometown Akita for the spring tour. Please keep up the good work.
Thank you very much.
What do you mean by "yokatabi"?
It's not bewitching.
Neither was I. What do you mean by "bewitching"?
I don't think it's bewitching.
It's not bewitching.
I did it.
That's amazing.
You might do it.
Yuyu-chan.
I've been supporting Yuna-chan since her audition,
I'm happy to be able to support Yuna-chan in Ebichu like this.
Thanks to Yuna-chan, I am truly happy to be a resident of Fukuoka Prefecture.
I am always energized by your cool singing voice that I can't imagine from your cute figure.
Please let me continue to watch over Yuna-chan's growth.
I will always love you. Thank you very much.
Elevated view.
Elevated view, I'm with you.
Thank you very much.
Mr. Jochen, Mr. Sakuragi Paisen, please give us a few words to get us fired up.
Let's do our best today!
I think he's still full of steam.
It's okay, right? It's in the morning.
Yes, it's in the morning.
It's already afternoon.
Let's work hard this afternoon.
No. 5, huh?
Thank you very much, Pechidan.
If you come to Iwate, please eat cold noodles.
I want to eat.
Okay, I'll pull out the bulks.
You've done a good job of conveying the charm of cold noodles, haven't you?
Shio-san, I'm looking forward to seeing you in your costume for this year's birthday live.
What should I do? I'm thinking about it a lot. I have several candidates.
I have.
I do.
That was quick.
Yes, I have several things I want to do.
I have a lot of ideas, too.
Okay.
Here you go. Oh, wow. Shiori-chan. Nice to meet you, Emma. I'm usually a Batten Girls' Club geek.
Actually, when Emma-chan joined, I was surprised to see how much she and I looked alike. LOL. But I still can't compare to her beautiful smile and aura.
I will use her makeup, etc. as a reference. I support not only your activities as a member of Ebichu, but also as a model.
I will come to see you at a live concert with my honey orange penra. Please take care of yourself and enjoy Ebi Junior.
Thank you very much. I see the resemblance. I'm curious.
I want to see it. I'd like to see it.
Thank you very much.
I'll be there.
Chihiro, thank you for always bringing smiles to my face.
Yuno heals me every day. I want you to tell me that you love me.
I love you.
Kyon!
Thank you so much.
Oh no.
That's all.
Thank you, Aro-san.
I have been wondering about this for a long time, but with Hinata's graduation, I have made a donation to Kuna-san.
Thank you very much.
I went to see the star down the street and was happy to see the street with the zombie pose that I had longed for.
And I was able to take Ibaraki pictures of Haru-chan.And I was able to take Haru-chan's Ibaraki.
I'm looking forward to the live outside game and will wait for it.
Thank you very much.
Ibaraki performance.
Please look forward to it.
Yay!
I can't get a shot.
I could take it.
Shio-san, thank you for supporting Spicomi!
It's over, Spicomi!
Three questions!
Takayu's voice inside...
Ah!
The deep voice inside is Ueto Ayasan!
Ueto and Ayasan, I'm sorry...
No, no, no, I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry, but I think you sound like Ueto Aya.
I'd like you to practice a few things and show us where you're going.
I'm sorry, I didn't recognize you for a second.
I'm sorry, I lost it for a second.
You know Ueto Aya, right?
Of course I know her.
I've seen you on TV recently.
What's going on?
What kind of way?
What do you mean, what do you mean?
Calm down.
Necci-chan, I fell in love with your braids at the camp.
I fell in love even more with her strong core singing voice
I fell in love even more with her core and strong singing voice.
I'm sure you must have been so nervous that I can't even imagine how nervous you must have been.
But your voice far exceeded the expectations of the fans, and I couldn't help but cry.
Can I tell you a lot about Ema-chan from now on?
Thank you very much for your letter.
Oh, I made a mistake.
I'm Nakamura.
Nakamura.
Atsushi, I will always support you, so please do your best!
Thank you very much. I will do my best.
Meki-chan, I'm looking forward to your role in the spring tour.
Thank you very much.
Oh, is it okay?
Yes, it is.
Thank you, Shiori-chan.
What kind of girl do you like? Makeup, hairstyle, atmosphere, and so on.
I like girls with long blonde hair or short blue hair,
I like girls with long blonde hair or short blue hair, especially if they have an open bottom.
I like girls with pierced ears,
I also like girls who wear vintage clothes.
But I also really like girls who wear clothes that are mine,
Yuu doesn't wear pretty, frilly clothes,
I think girls who wear such clothes are very cute,
Girls who wear simple clothes are also cute.
And you all are too.
That's why they are all cute.
In the end, Yuno's boyfriend is the cutest.
Yes.
Mr. Pentan, thank you for entering college.
I was so moved by the way you all worked so hard.
Please tell us if there is any song or performance that left a lasting impression on you.
Yes, I do. It left an impression on me.
But there is one that I just thought was amazing,
You know how Singalong Singathon got frizzy in the middle?
I was thinking, "Let's get all the team members more involved in that part,
I was impressed by that,
That part left a great impression on me.
Thank you very much.
I will go from there.
Thank you very much, Kurukuru-chan. I'm glad to have you in Ebichu. Thank you so much. I love you so much, Emaino-chan.
This is totally unrelated, but what is your favorite Sanrio character? By the way, I guess Korokoro Kuririn. I've been guessing more and more in Ebichu.
Sanrio character? Kuromi?
Kochakko.
Matsumaru-kun.
I don't know. Sanrio?
Nyan-nyan.
Kitty-chan, right?
Kitty-chan is Sanrio.
Nakamura, I'll pull it.
Yes, I'm pulling for you.
Canto-san, Yuna-chan, I'm cheering for you from Oita. Thank you very much.Kant, Yuna, I support you from Oita. Thank you very much.
Thank you from Oita.
Thank you very much. Then, I would like to draw the last card one by one.
Okay.
The last one.
That was quick.
So fast.
What should I do?
Oh, there are so many.
I'll get the bomb guy.
Here we go.
Thank you, Mr. Yoshiwa. I'm looking forward to seeing Yuna's future in Cocoyo.
Thank you very much.
Okay, I'm going to pull out Inoue.
Okay.
Okay. From the bunch.
I can't get it.
Got it!
All right!
We are always rooting for you, Mr. Motoki. Keep up the good work. Thank you very much.
Okay! Now, I will take the last pull.
Please pull, please pull.
I hope you can pull it.
You're the cutest, so I won't do it. The very last.
Haruna, I love you. I love you too. Thank you very much.
Okay, I'll go last.
Yes, sir.
Ah!
Mikachan.
University Geikai Costume
The colors are lovely and the
It's one of my favorite costumes, and the shape is lovely.
I'm glad I can keep it with me as a checkerboard!
What is your favorite costume?
I don't know...
I don't know, but I've always loved that one. The costume from last year's school festival was very Pretty Cure-like.
Boot costume? Yes. So much.
I think it's cute.
Yes, I'm pulling for you, Nakamura.
I'm rooting for you, Mr. Fluffy. Thank you very much.
Thank you, Fluffy.
Oh, you mean the one who didn't get invited.
Ah...
No, we still have our plain clothes on
Our plain clothes-style outfits.
That's right, the plain clothes outfit we're wearing right now.
Isn't it cute?
It's so cute.
It's kind of a costume that fits our personalities.
It fits.
It's so cute.
I wish you all the best in giving it to us.
We'll do our best.
Thank you for your hard work.
I wish Emma could wear the reboot outfit.
Indeed.
I'm sure.
It's nice.
Next time
Next time.
Let's go for it!
Congratulations, winners!
Congratulations to the winners.
I hope you win. I hope you win.
I hope you win.
The roll is coming off.
It comes right off.
Some people do.
I'll change the color of the letters in your name.
Thank you very much.
I don't know what I'm gonna do next.
I'm going to put on my switch cool outfit.
I'd like to wear it.
Yes, the Switchcool Costume.
Really cute.
Cute, they are all cute!
Thank you, Akira and Chiba!
What a dependable MC! I look forward to it every week!
Thank you for listening every week!
Please send me your e-mails too!
Kenken, thank you very much. I always admire your alright pace!Thank you, Kenken. I always admire your alright pace.
I want to be a person like you, Mr. Ginopi. I'm glad.
I'm glad.
Okay, I'll go ahead and draw. May I draw.
That's it! Oh! You wrote a lot.
Bun-chan!
Hello, Non-chan! Thank you for choosing me! I always support you.
I'm looking forward to seeing you in high school as well,
I am looking forward to seeing her again at this year's birthday party.
By the way, if there is anything you want to do in school or at BIC when you become a high school student, please let me know.
I love Non-chan! Thank you very much.
Let's see, what do you want to do in school when you become a high school student?
Well, I think that in high school, I will be able to take classes that I didn't take in junior high school,
I am really looking forward to that.
Also, I would like to do my best in Bichu.
I think that in junior high school, there were a lot of tests and things, so it was a lot of work,
I am looking forward to that,
I want to do my best in Bijutsu.
Oh, no. I was at Sue-chan's place. Watch out.
My arms are working in both directions.
Um, let's go.
Yes. Thank you, Toki.
First of all, thank you for joining Ebichu. I was shot out of my skin when I saw Emma-chan's performance and smile at the college arts and crafts show.
I'm Emma-chan from now on, along with my top pick, Po-senpai. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Nell-kun.
Hello Yuna-chan.
Thank you for the Omiya free live.
I fell in love with you at first sight at the university alert and became a Yuna-chan guesser, and I was really happy to meet you for the first time.
I was so happy that I cried, and with my tears, an ocean formed and fish started to live in it,
The fishes lived there.
I kicked a big stone, and animals and humans started to live on the earth.
Please forget about it.
I'm going to Tokunan, so I'll see you there.
You look lovely today.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for coming to both Omiya and Deoknam.
I'm looking forward to seeing you again.
Thank you very much, Mr. Marpon. I'm going to participate in the reservation last week for the spring tour with a big welcome Devil.
I'll be waiting for you. Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you Hideko and Alexa! We had a great time at the free show at Canal City Fukuoka!
We took the cutest pictures in the world. I'm glad you enjoyed it.
It was fun.
Okay, I'll go now.
All right, Miss Harrah's.
I'm down two.
Wow, that's great, great, great, great!
I'm looking forward to the spring tour. Thank you.
Wow, that's happening again today.
Thank you very much.
Thank you, Seventh Color Beetle.
Thank you for joining M-Chu. I'm sure it will help the group grow.
Thank you. Let's make it big.
Let's make it big.
I'm feeling strong
Nakamura, I'll pull
Arisa, Yuna's song really moved me Yuna, keep up the good work
I'll do my best, thank you
Sakura, I'll pull.
Oh, it's a long sentence. Thank you.
Hello, Positive Leo, Sakuragekokona.
Hello.
I would like to announce my favorite part of Sakurage Kokona-san.
Her singing voice.
I love it a lot. I love the dancer who knows how to show herself.
I love that she can work hard and straight toward her goals.
I love that they have interesting stories.
I love that they are clear about what they like and what they are not interested in.
I love that she is sometimes very human.
And I love her cute face.
I will always love you.
Wow, I'm so happy! I love you too. Let's go together.
I'll go with you.
Yes!
Can't you get it?
Got it?
Thank you, Mr. Onichi.
Do you have any recommendations for shark sake in Ehime?
I don't know, it's not fashionable to tell saunas.
Please ask Mayama, Aya and Miire-chan.Ask Mayama, Aya and Miire-chan.
There's a lot of good food here, pretty much.
I see.
Maichan.
Thank you very much. I love Nonoka-chan's sparkling eyes. I would like to learn from Nonoka-chan's hard-working spirit even more.
I will start working as a nursery teacher in April. Thank you very much. I look forward to seeing you again at Spring Tour Ichikawa.
I know it must be tough being a nursery teacher, but please do your best. Thank you very much.
I will draw an ema.
Thank you, Yuki-chan.
I love Emma-chan's relaxed smile and spontaneous singing voice.
I look forward to seeing various Emma-chan.
Thank you very much. Please come to the show.
I will be there.
Hi, Mr. Yotsuki-kun, Mr. Nakamura, Hi!
I usually enjoy your singing voice...oh no, it's not that, it's just that after I heard your voice at Makuhari Mesute, my life has become more enjoyable.
Your normal speaking voice is great, but your singing voice is even better.
Please let me hear your singing voice again.
Well then, hello, hello, hello, hello, I'm back.
Thank you very much.
Yes, ma'am.
Mr. Yoshijima-kun. Thank you very much.
I draw picture books, and someday if my work is made into an animated film,
I would like to have the BTOB members do the voices of the characters.
When that time comes, I would appreciate it very much.
The characters are a dog and a cat.
Oh, wow.
That's great.
A dog and a cat.
I didn't know that. A dog and a cat.
I'd like to be a voice actor.
Thank you, Mr. Sakasan. Thank you very much.
I will go after the spring tour. I am looking forward to it.
Thank you very much. I am looking forward to the next one.
I will go.
Is that you?
Hello, Nonoka-chan.
My real name is Nonoka, too.
I wrote "Nonoka" and then I wrote...
What's this? Is it the character for "Fumi"?
It's written Fumi.
It's been a while. Isn't it Fumi?
What? This is Yuno's.
The same kanji is written for Yuno's.
I heard it's written as "hoo".
Cheki! It was Cheki's name and Fumi.
I love you, Yuno-chan. Heart. Thank you. We have the same name.
You don't read this as Fumi, do you?
No, I don't read it.
I don't read it.
You don't read it.
I always thought it was Fumi.
I'm sure that's not true.
I'll read the sentence that says "Fumi" too, but I don't think it's true.
I'm sorry.
I pulled it out.
Thank you, Goriken.
Ema-chan's smile is really wonderful and I love it. Her performance is so majestic that I can't believe she just joined the band.
I will join the tour this year. Thank you so much.
I look forward to seeing you in Tohoku. I will continue to support you.
Thank you very much. I will be waiting for you from Tohoku. Thank you very much.
I'll pull it out.
Ayano-chan. Yuna-chan is cute and I love her. I love you too. Thank you very much.
I'll go.
Thank you, Hina-chan.
Thanks to Ogura-chan, I've become a fan,
I want to follow Ebitu in 2023 as well.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Please continue to be sexy, cute and cool, and do your best as Ogura-chan.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad.
I make it easy to live.
I can't take a picture because two pictures overlap.
I can't take a picture because my fingers are dry.
There is winter
Maybe it's not winter anymore.
Three pictures I couldn't take.
Thank you, Ayukoro!
Yunopi's smile really cheers me up!Yunopi's smile really cheers me up.
Seeing you working so hard makes me want to work hard, too.
I'm really happy to have met Yunopi.
I love you so much that Yunopi will keep coming through from now on.
I hope that Yunopi will be able to keep coming through from now on.
I love you!
I'm really looking forward to the tour, and I'll be there for Omaki's love debut before that.
I can't wait to meet you and cheer for you at the show.
That's my second one too, Necchi.
I fell in love with your braids at the camp.
I couldn't imagine her voice from her usual cute and fluffy way of speaking, but it was so strong and powerful that it made me feel even better.
I'm sure you must have been so nervous that I can't even imagine, but your voice exceeded the expectations of the fans and I couldn't help but cry.
Can I talk a lot about Emma from now on? Please push me to the next level, because I've already drawn two tickets!
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much!
Yuki-chan, I love Yuna-chan's cute and fragile singing voice, her core character, and her strong attitude.
And I am looking forward to seeing what kind of Yuna-chan you will be in the future.
I will shake a lot of milk tea to find her.
Please shake lots of milk tea. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Haruka-san, my name is Haruka.
I used to listen to Ebichu because I liked their songs, but when I saw the audition video for 2021, I fell in love with Cocona at first sight.
This is my first female idol guess.
Thank you for the fresh scene.
She is one year rougher than Coco, but even as a woman, she is really cute and her face is a big winner.
I love her wonderful singing voice, her sharp dance moves, her genius expression management, and now I love everything about her.
I will continue to support you. I love you from the bottom of my heart. I am so happy.
Thank you for seeing me so much. I love you too.
Thank you very much.
Mark-n-dot-at-mark
Thank you very much, Markn at Mark Ikuko.
Yunapi's performance in the drama was too nice.
It was too good. Is she an actress in the future?
I wonder.
It was really interesting.
All in all.
I'm going to go now.
Petsika.
Now that there are 10 members, Ebitu is fresh and powerful, and I'm really looking forward to seeing them in the future. I am looking forward to seeing them on the spring tour. Thank you very much. See you on the spring tour.
Thank you very much.
Yes, thank you, Akito.
I am surprised that you can sing so well. Thank you for joining Ebichu. I am looking forward to the spring tour. Thank you very much.
Thank you, Ms. Funakura, for your hard work at Spicomi. I was happy to hear many things that Yuna-san talked about.
She was cute, cool and fun. Thank you very much. I will deliver a lot more in the future.
Hay fever? It's bad.
I know.
It's bad, isn't it?
I have hay fever.
My hay fever gauge is at max.
Ew.
Do you have any special points about the clothes you are wearing today, or anything you would like to say to the housers?
The point of my clothes is that they are all torn.
It's ripped all over.
I don't think you can see it, but can I stand up?
Wow.
It's ripped.
There is no more cloth. There is no more cloth.
Spring tour, yes. We have Ibaraki again, so we will have fun again this year,
Well, I would like to cherish each and every performance. I will do my best.
Yes, I'll do my best.
Okay, I got it.
Thank you for your hard work, Udarai-san and Ebiju-chan.
My last year's training was to strengthen my torso, but it didn't work at all.
So, could you please give me a shout out so that I can do my best this year?
Thank you very much.
Did you set a goal to train your torso?
Good luck.
Do your best.
Work out. Work out. Work hard.
Okay, I'm going.
Denden-san,
I am always encouraged by the way Nonakamaru works hard downwards. And their live performances are so accomplished that it's hard to believe they've been a member for less than two years,
Recently, he has been working as an actor and demonstrating his MC skills on the radio and in the distribution channel, so it is a pleasure to see Nonakamaru active in a variety of situations.
I believe that Nonakamaru's efforts will become an even greater strength for Ebitu. I will continue to support you all the way.
Thank you very much. I will do my best to do various jobs. Good luck!
Karen, I love your bang bang beat, Ema-chan.
Wow, thank you very much.
Bang bang beat.Bang bang beat.
Eh, stop right there.
How do you read that?
Hmm?
Takasu Takashi?
Where?
Kisuke?
Takasu Takasu?
Taka, right? Maybe not Takasu? Here.
Maybe it's Taka.
Yes, you're Takasu Takasu.
Takasu Takasu?
Takayuki?
I don't know.
Takayuki.
I'm sorry if I'm wrong.
Is Ms. Takayuki home?
Mr. Takayuki?
Are you there?
I love Yuna-chan and her cool singing voice and cute smile.
I'll be waiting for you in Osaka for the spring tour. Please come visit us in Kobe again. I'm going to Kobe again.
I'm looking forward to the spring tour in Osaka. Thank you very much.
Yes, I couldn't tie the ribbon today.
Was it ok? I'm fine, I'm fine.
Yes, thank you very much. Thank you, Ayumi.
Hello, everyone at L-CHANNEL!
Hello.
It has ended safely as a spring tour.
I live in Ibaraki prefecture,
Coconut-chan joined Ebitun and I was so happy to see Ebitun live in my hometown,
I am very happy to hear that I can now see Ebitun live in my hometown,
I am very happy.
Coconut is the star of Ibaraki.
I am really looking forward to the spring tour.
See you in Ibaraki.
I'm so happy. I love Ibaraki.
Thank you Bobby Festa.
Hello Yunopi members.
Hello.
I went to see the free live performance of the middle age members, Omiya.
I was impressed by the way they were so dynamic without the elderly members.
I am going to see Yunopi's birthday live next time, so I am looking forward to seeing her growing up.
I am sure you are all imagining that Yuno's birthday live is going to be amazing,
I'm not sure if it is too much or too little.
It's just a normal concert, so don't expect too much.
Don't expect too much.
I'll be going then.
Nacchan-san. Nononon, Nanakimaru is very cute.
I love Nanahimaru's singing voice, and I also love the fact that she is a little girl.
I am completely captivated. Please take care of your health and I will continue to support you.
Thank you for always making me feel cheerful. Thank you very much.
Yes, I will go.
Yes, I will.
Yes, thank you, Ume-kun.
I've been secretly supporting you since the live performance of the new organization.
I will continue to support you. Thank you very much.
Thank you, Mr. Ume-kun.
I became a fan of Yuna-chan after I got to know her at the audition.
I like Yuna-chan's Hakata dialect because it is very cute.
Hakata dialect is cute, isn't it?
Hakata dialect is cute.
That Nagoya dialect is too hard to listen to.
It's not well-liked.
Oh, that's right.
Akane is cute.
Kyushu people are cute.
They're cute.
I admire them a lot.
I really admire Kyoto dialect.
That's for sure.
It's cute.
Like Christmas.
Yes, thank you, Nappo, for the live instrument.
Hello!
Hello! I'm Nappo, a certified Junior Oystermeister under the influence of Kona-chan.
Thank you very much. I would be happy if you like it. Writing is difficult to write in Kanji, isn't it?
By the way, I have been hit 3 times so far, but still I can't stop playing live instruments.
It's strong. I am also a live instrument person, but the best recommendation is Akkeshi-san in Hokkaido?
What is this? Akkeshi?What is this? Is it a fake?
Is it "Akkeshi"?
It's "Akkeshi" from "Akkeshi-kun's Abnormal Revolution", isn't it?
Akkeshi.
I learned that from a song by Campanella Weekday.
I think it was Akkeshi.
They are called "akkeshi," and they cost about 200 yen each at the local market.
Easy! I want some!
I had a taco with fried oysters in it the other day.
Oh, that kind of thing is good, too. It was so delicious.
Now, here's a question. How many times did I say "oyster"?
Five times.
Four times.
Three.
Three. Four.
You didn't include the name. 1.
2 3
4 5
Congratulations!
Wow, Acky, you know him!
Oh, I knew it! Please listen to Wednesday Sanpanella's song, everyone!
Thank you, Yuri! Thank you so much for coming to Kobe today for the free concert!
It was great to see you guys perform up close. You were so cute. Thank you, so cute.
I'm off!
Thank you, Ietto neezo-san... you're always so serious, Nonakamaru-san...
What do you do when you don't have a bite?
When he's not chewing his nose?
Not round?
When is it not round?
Well, I'm sleepy.
I have to study for a test.
Or...
And... and... and... and... and...
I understand.
That's when I don't study for the test.
I did it 10 minutes before the test and I got it right.
Oh, really?
I'll pull it.
Yuki.
I love Riko and Emma. I'm so excited every day.
I wear Ebitu T-shirts at work.
I just love Ebitu.
I love Riko and Emma.
I'll be forever in love with Ebitu. Thank you very much.
Wow, you wear Ebituju at work too?
Great, keep up the good work!
Work hard!
Go for it!
Nakamura, I'll pull it.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Tatsuya. I applied for the first time for the online autograph session.
Yuna-chan has been too cute lately. I am looking forward to seeing her growth more and more. Thank you very much. I hope I will be troubled more.
Wow.
Hi Oscar. Hello from Mexico.
Mexico!
Hello.
No.
Namotsu.
Namotsu is not India.
Namaste is Mexico.
Do you understand? I don't know. I don't know. Well, hello anyway.
Thank you so much.
Wow, that's great. I'm so happy.
Can I go next time? Yes, you can.
All right.
I can't get it. I want the top one.
You can't get it.
Yuka-chan, I'm cheering for you from Hokkaido. This is your second time, isn't it?
No, I heard it from someone else, didn't I, Yuka-chan?
I wonder if Yuka-chan pulled it out earlier.
Is it me?
You asked me earlier.
That's great.
Thank you.
Next, me. I'll go.
Here we go. Oh, no, no, no, it won't come off, it won't come off, it won't come off. I got it!
Here it is. Miki Noguchi. Thank you very much.Yes, I am. Miki Noguchi. Thank you very much.
It is wonderful that Ebitu is always the embodiment of the best and strongest at that time.
You always give me energy. I will always love you.
Thank you very much. Please come to our live concert or something.
I'll be there. I'll be there.
Yay.
Tomoki-san. Thank you very much.
Can you all go?
This is the third time for all of you.
That's great!
Thank you, Kameta-san, for your always enjoyable live performances.
I am also from Fukuoka, so I feel very close to you.
Thank you for being in Fukuoka as well. Please go, Haru-chan.
Yes, Naru-chan.
Coconut-chan's dance is so cool, I love it. Thank you very much.
I'm glad.
Yes, Mr. Kazuukun. Thank you very much.
It's almost your birthday, isn't it? Happy birthday.
I'm sorry I didn't win the birthday solo live,
I'm glad Hino-chan is so popular. Good luck with the live.
I'm looking forward to seeing you at the live.
Yay!
Please check out the live streaming.
We have live photos and socks, so please do. I want socks.
Okay, I'll go then.
Mikitty-san. I can do my best, too, seeing the reliable cloth camera that has become a little older sister. Shine more and more.
You are shining. Thank you very much.
Kiran Kiran.
Yes.
That's great, great.
Kazuchan.
Yes.
Background, Sakurai Yama-chan. I met her for the first time in Kobe the other day and thought she was very cute. I look forward to working with you in the future.
Keifu?
Keifu. Thank you very much.
Keifu. Great. You're very kind. Thank you very much.
I'll be going.
Ryohei-san. Ebiturkey member. I have nothing but expectations. Thank you very much. I will work harder.
I'll do my best.
He said he'll buy the photos and the kutsuroi.
Thank you very much.
It's not relaxing.
I just signed the photos,
I wrote all of them. I signed all of them.
Thank you, Mr. Uccarin.
Second time.
Thank you, Ebichu.
Thanks for your hard work.
My last year's was for core training,
It was not good at all.
So, can you give me ale so that I can do my best this year?
I have enough ale for two people.
Please do your best. I'm already working out.
Please do your best.
I'll be rooting for you.
Ayu.
AYU. Thank you very much.
GINOPY. I can't take my eyes off of it lately because of its cute and mysterious charm. I will continue to support you.
Thank you very much.
I'll be there!
Whopper whopper!
Jangan!
Suna-chan.
Wild Okachan. I call you "baby" because you look like a baby.
Can I finger you like a baby?
Yes!
I'll give you special permission.
Let's use a different one instead of this one.
Yes.
Sorry. It's not here again.
Oh, no.
Minminjamisachi, and it's the second one. Thank you very much.
Next, Ms. Yanagina?
Yes. I made a note again.
Don't note.
I read the comments.
Skye, this is the second time.
No comments again.
Thank you.
No comments.No comments.
Yes, I'm going.
Mai, I look at your instagram and other places for clothing and makeup reference.
Do you have any favorite cosmetics or clothing brands?
Lately, Q.10 has been taking the place of my eyes.
Is it going to end today?
Is today the last day?
Yes, it is.
Oh, why are you talking like this?
Well, you know, if you're looking for something that's good for your eyes, I recommend Lofand's, uh, lipstick. Oh, I bought the one you recommended.
Oh, really? It's so easy to use. The matte one.
Thank you, Unachi. Babu Babu is cute. Baby Yuunopi is so cute and I want to congratulate her. Please keep on being Babudan. I love you.
Thank you very much. I'm going. I'll grow up soon.
Good boy. Here we go.
I think I'll go this way. This one, this one, this one.
I love you, Mr. Okasan. Thank you very much.
Mr. Okasa!
Yes, Mr. Okasa!
Mr. Kazukiku is always smiling and cute Thank you
Nikko
Nikko, a little low
Yuna
Please go!
I support you a lot.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'll do my best.
Okay, last one for each of you.
Okay.
I'm off now.
See you later!
See you later.
Good luck
Prayers, everyone.
Pray for me.
Pray.
This person...
Chisato!
I fell in love with Ms. Sakuragi when I saw her solo dance in the reboot, and I've been pushing her more and more. I love her so much that I cried at her birthday party.
I love her singing and dancing. I love her projection. Thank you. I love everyone who says they love me.
I love you! Thank you!
Thank you so much Yunopi, I love you so much Thank you
Just a quick one
One goodbye, please
Jansan!
Thank you, Mona
Congratulations on your graduation from junior high school.
I'm sure you'll be starting a new life, and I'm happy for you if you're healthy and happy.
I'll be cheering for you from behind the scenes. I'll be graduating in a little while. I'll do my best in high school. Thank you.
Sakura, I'll go last!
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much, Mr. Lukeka. I'm looking forward to the spring tour. Thank you.
This is Mr. Nakamura. I'll pull. I'll pull the last one.
Himajin1133, thank you for joining Ebichu.
I fell in love with you just after hearing one phrase of the first song at the first live performance at the university arts department after you joined.
I feel that the mocking and a little originality will be the new characteristics of the new insects.
Please continue to blow a new wind.
I will. Thank you very much.
I'll let it blow.
Yes, so we are done.
Thank you very much.
I know some of you did not win,
Please sign the autograph, I have it.
Please look forward to receiving it.
That's all I have to say.
How was it? Everyone. It's amazing. 900 people have watched it.
Thank you very much.
Really? Thank you very much.
In the middle of the day on a Sunday.
Thank you very much.
It's Sunday, so everyone is closed, right?
That's right. That's for sure. You'll be working tomorrow, right?
Let's go to school or something.
Let's do our best.
Tomorrow is the music video shoot.
As an extra.
Extra. I'd appreciate it if you don't tell Ekio or anyone else about it yet.
I'm looking forward to it. What kind of music will be released? Please look forward to it.I am looking forward to it. What kind of songs will be released? Please look forward to it.
Thank you very much. It was a great weekend.
I'm 10 minutes happy. I'm really looking forward to it. Thank you very much.
I will write about it.
I took a lot of pictures.
I have more variations of poses.
It was really fun.
So, thank you all very much.
Thank you very much.
This is the end.
That's all for us,
C.T.B.T.A.C.
Bye bye.
Looking forward to seeing you again.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.